that must be...
谁来了
-Heather! -Get her!
-新竹-抓住她
That rhymes!
真押韵呀
You must stay...
你必须呆在
In your cell. How many  times do we have to tell you?
你的牢房 我们还要告诉你多少次
It's me, you muttonheads!
使我 你们这些傻瓜
Whoa.
哇
Wow!
喔
Uh, sorry, Astrid. Totally unconvincing.
额，对不起 烈女 你化妆技术太好了
Oh, yeah, I could tell.
哦 是吗 我看得出来
Are you sure about this?
你确定你要这样做
No, but it's our only chance.
是得  这是我们唯一的机会
We'll be shadowing you from the sky.
我们会在天空掩护你的
I don't need shadowing.
我不需要掩护
Just in case.
只是避免万一
You know, it'll make me feel better.
你知道  这样我会放心一点
Fine. Just stay out of sight.
好吧  那就呆在视线之外
If Alvin sees you, it'll all be over.
如果雄霸看见你 计划就泡汤了
Don't worry about us.
别担心我们了
Just get the book and get out of there.
只管去把书拿回啦
We'll be waiting.
我们会一直等待
Hey, Astrid... be safe.
嘿  烈女  注意安全